# NOAM ACKERMAN

# **Frontend Developer**

# **About Myself**

I'm Noam Ackerman, a frontend developer experienced in React, Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, and more. I'm not just a coder but also a versatile musician and visual artist. I thrive on challenges, I'm a quick learner, problem solver, and a highly creative individual. I value healthy and productive communication.

# **Experience**

#### Flare - Linkedin link

Frontend Engineer

2024 - present

- I collaborate with numerous teams to deliver data-driven features from Figma to production for complex online funnels, marketing acquisition pages and web apps for attorneys and customers.
- I develop with technologies including Next.js, React, TypeScript, Tailwind, Git, Builder.io, UI libraries (Radix and Schadon), React Testing Library, Jest/Vitest and more.
- I focus on clean, reusable code by creating reusable components, custom hooks and shared utility functions.
- I contributed to frontend guild initiatives, including monorepo convention guidelines and the company's new design system.

# PlayTracker - Website link

Freelancer Developer

2023 - 2024

- I researched gaming platform and games APIs through official docs, third-party libraries, and network sniffing.
- I designed solutions for retrieving player profiles and stats across platforms.
- I developed interactive user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

#### Nosto Solutions - Website link

Frontend Developer

2021 - 2023

- I developed dynamic, responsive merchant interfaces used daily by thousands, using ReactJS, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, and jQuery.
- I owned features from Figma to production, managing Jira tickets and resolving bugs through merchant site investigations.
- I designed UI mockups, wireframes, and improved UX.
- I initiated and guided a new team workflow, created documents to boost productivity, and optimized project management efficiency.

#### **Portfolio**

Check out my Portfolio at - noamackerman.com

# Education

Front-end, React and responsive web development

SheCodes USA, 2021

Epic React - Course for Advanced React

Kent C. Dodds, 2023

Online Courses for TypeScript and for NodeJS

2023

#### Contact

+972505954084

developer.noam@gmail.com

www.noamackerman.com

github.com/noam-ackerman

in <u>linkedin.com/in/noam-</u> <u>ackerman/</u>

# **Skills**

ReactJS & NextJS

JavaScript & TypeScript

**UI** libraries

CSS & Tailwind & Sass

**HTML** 

Git

Firebase

**Responsive Development** 

Jest & React-testing-library

# Tools

VS code

Figma

Photoshop

Jira

Slack

Builder.io (CMS)

# Languages

Hebrew - Native

**English - Fluent**